[Music]
frozen in a crowded
room full of
strangers Where are you my
love my
love will I taste your kiss again
tell me this is not the end for
us For
us Hey can you hear me wherever you are
i'm praying to angels and wishing on
stars that we'll find each other no
matter how far Cuz 5,000
miles is breaking my
[Music]
heart You don't need to take the blame
We'll make it through
this space
somehow
Someday Hey can you hear me wherever you
are i'm praying to angels and wishing on
stars that we'll find each other No
matter how far cuz 5,000
miles is breaking my heart and just your
voice on the other end of the
telephone
Oh I
hate I need your touch that lets me know
you're holding me and you never let go
at this
time Hey can you hear me wherever you
are I'm praying to angels and wishing on
stars We'll find each other no matter
how far Cuz 5,000
rounds is breaking my heart
that and we'll find each
other Cuz 5,000 5,000 miles is breaking
my heart
Breaking my heart
[Music]